checkpoint.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Check Point Software

### CHECK POINT PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy explains how we use the personal information that Check Point collects or generates both in relation to the Check Point website ([www.checkpoint.com](https://www.checkpoint.com/)) and our products and services.

The list below sets out what is covered in this Privacy Policy and you can click on the headings to go to a specific section.

  1.  **BACKGROUND**
  2.  **THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES WE PROVIDE**
  3.  **THE TYPES OF PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT**
  4.  **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**
  5.  **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**
  6.  **INTERNATIONAL** **TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL DATA**
  7.  **HOW WE SAFEGUARD YOUR INFORMATION**
  8.  **HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL DATA**
  9.  **YOUR RIGHTS**
  10.  **DESIGNATED REPRESENTATIVE**
  11.  **QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS**

  1.  **BACKGROUND**
    1. Check Point Software Technologies Ltd. with its registered office at 5 Shlomo Kaplan Street, Tel Aviv 67897, Israel (email: [privacy_inquiries@checkpoint.com](mailto:privacy_inquiries\(at\)checkpoint.com)) and other companies in the Check Point group collect and use certain Personal Data. Check Point is responsible for ensuring that it uses that Personal Data in compliance with data protection laws.
    2. At Check Point we respect the privacy of our clients and we are committed to keeping all your Personal Data secure. This Privacy Policy governs the handling of Personal Data by Check Point in the course of carrying on commercial activities.
    3. We use the following definitions in this Privacy Policy: **“Check Point”, “we” or “us”** means Check Point Software Technologies Ltd. and other companies in the Check Point group. **“Personal Data”** means any data which relates to a living individual who can be identified from that data or from that data and other information which is in the possession of, or is likely to come into the possession of, Check Point (or its representatives or service providers). In addition to factual information, it includes any expression of opinion about an individual and any indication of the intentions of Check Point or any other person in respect of an individual.
  2.  **THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES WE PROVIDE**
    1. This Privacy Policy concerns the following categories of information that we collect about you when providing the following products and services:  

      1.  **)** Information we receive through our websites (e.g. www.checkpoint.com) ( **“Check Point Websites”** );
      2.  **)** Information we receive through our products ( **“Check Point Products”** );
      3.  **)** Information we receive through our support, mobile security solution or cloud-based services ( **“Check Point Services”** ).
  3.  **THE TYPES OF PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT**
    1. Many of the services offered by Check Point require us to obtain Personal Data about you in order to perform the services we have been engaged to provide. In relation to each of the services described at paragraph 2.1 above, we will collect and process the following Personal Data about you:
      *  **Information that you provide to Check Point**. This includes information about you that you provide to us. The nature of the services you are requesting will determine the kind of Personal Data we might ask for, though such information may include (by way of a non-exhaustive list):
        * basic Personal Data (such as first name; family name; position in the company [ _title_ ]; company name; company email address; business phone number; business address; city; postcode; country);
        * any information that you choose to share on Check Point internet forums which may be considered Personal Data. (Please note that Check Point does not collate information included on Check Point internet forums together with Personal Data from your User Center account or profile);
      *  **Information that we collect or generate about you.** This includes (by way of non-exhaustive list):
        * a file with your contact history to be used for enquiry purposes so that we may ensure that you are satisfied with the services which we have provided to you;
        * through our cloud security services, traffic and security reports that include information on the internet usage of the organization’s computer users (e.g. what websites were visited by each user, any documents downloaded, security incidents, prevention measures taken by the gateway, etc.); and
        * activity data relating to the use of protected documents, such as altering a document’s permissions and information regarding the individual that performed the activity.
      *  **Cookies.**
        * When you visit Check Point Websites, cookies are used to collect technical information about the services that you use, and how you use them.
        * For more information on the cookies used by Check Point, please see the **Check Point Cookies Notice** tab on this page.
      *  **Anonymized data.**
        * In addition to the categories of Personal Data described above, Check Point will also process further anonymized information and data that is not processed by reference to a specific individual.
  4.  **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**
    1. Your Personal Data may be stored and processed by us in the following ways and for the following purposes:
      * for ongoing review and improvement of the information provided on Check Point Websites to ensure they are user friendly and to prevent any potential disruptions or cyber attacks;
      * to allow you to use and access the functionality provided by the Check Point Products;
      * to assess your application for Check Point Products, where applicable;
      * to set up customers to use Check Point Products;
      * to set up users to use the User Center;
      * to conduct analysis required to detect malicious data and understand how this may affect your IT system;
      * for statistical monitoring and analysis of current attacks on devices and systems and for the on-going adaptation of the solutions provided to secure devices and systems against current attacks;
      * to understand feedback on Check Point Products and to help provide more information on the use of those products and services quickly and easily;
      * to communicate with you in order to provide you with services or information about Check Point and Check Point Products;
      * for in-depth threat analysis;
      * to understand your needs and interests;
      * for the management and administration of our business;
      * in order to comply with and in order to assess compliance with applicable laws, rules and regulations, and internal policies and procedures; or
      * for the administration and maintenance of databases storing Personal Data
      * to market Check Point’s products and services.
    2. However we use Personal Data we make sure that the usage complies with law and the law allows us and requires us to use Personal Data for a variety of reasons. These include:
      * we need to do so in order to perform its contractual obligations with its customers;
      * we have obtained your consent;
      * we have legal and regulatory obligations that we have to discharge;
      * we may need to do so in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights or for the purpose of legal proceedings;
      * the use of your Personal Data as described is necessary for our legitimate business interests, such as:
        * allowing us to effectively and efficiently manage and administer the operation of our business;
        * maintaining compliance with internal policies and procedures;
        * monitoring the use of our copyrighted materials;
        * enabling quick and easy access to information on Check Point Products;
        * offering optimal, up-to-date security solutions for mobile devices and IT systems; and
        * obtaining further knowledge of current threats to network security in order to update our security solutions and provide these to the market.
    3. We will take steps to ensure that the Personal Data is accessed only by employees of Check Point that have a need to do so for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
  5.  **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**
    1. We may share your Personal Data within the Check Point group of companies for the purposes described above.
    2. We may also share your Personal Data outside of the Check Point group for the following purposes:
      * with our business partners. For example, this could include our partners from whom you or your company or your organization purchased the Check Point product(s). Personal Data will only be transferred to a business partner who is contractually obliged to comply with appropriate data protection obligations and the relevant privacy and confidentiality legislation;
      * with third party agents and contractors for the purposes of providing services to us (for example, Check Point’s accountants, professional advisors, IT and communication and marketing providers and debt collectors). These third parties will be subject to appropriate data protection obligations and they will only use your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy;
      * to the extent required by law, for example if we are under a duty to disclose your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal obligation (including, without limitation, in order to comply with tax reporting requirements and disclosures to regulators), or to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights;
      * if we sell our business or assets, in which case we may need to disclose your Personal Data to the prospective buyer for due diligence purposes; and
      * if we are acquired by a third party, in which case the Personal Data held by us about you will be disclosed to the third party buyer.
  6.  **INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF PERSONAL DATA**
    1. Check Point is a global business. Our customers and our operations are spread around the world. As a result, we collect and transfer Personal Data on a global basis. That means that we may transfer your Personal Data to locations outside of your country.
    2. Where we transfer your Personal Data to another country outside the EEA, we will ensure that it is protected and transferred in a manner consistent with legal requirements. In relation to data being transferred outside of Europe, for example, this may be done in one of the following ways:
      * the country that we send the data to might be approved by the European Commission as offering an adequate level of protection for Personal Data (Israel is an approved country);
      * the recipient might have signed up to a contract based on “model contractual clauses” approved by the European Commission, obliging them to protect your Personal Data;
      * where the recipient is located in the US, it might be a certified member of the EU-US Privacy Shield scheme; or
      * in other circumstances the law may permit us to otherwise transfer your Personal Data outside Europe.
    3. You can obtain more details of the protection given to your Personal Data when it is transferred outside Europe (including a copy of the standard data protection clauses which we have entered into with recipients of your Personal Data) by contacting us as described in paragraph 11 below.
  7.  **HOW WE SAFEGUARD YOUR INFORMATION**
    1. We have extensive controls in place to maintain the security of our information and information systems. Client files are protected with safeguards according to the sensitivity of the relevant information. Appropriate controls (such as restricted access) are placed on our computer systems. Physical access to areas where Personal Data is gathered, processed or stored is limited to authorized employees.
    2. As a condition of employment, Check Point employees are required to follow all applicable laws and regulations, including in relation to data protection law. Access to sensitive Personal Data is limited to those employees who need to it to perform their roles. Unauthorized use or disclosure of confidential client information by a Check Point employee is prohibited and may result in disciplinary measures.
    3. When you contact a Check Point employee about your file, you may be asked for some Personal Data. This type of safeguard is designed to ensure that only you, or someone authorized by you, has access to your file.
  8.  **HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL DATA**
    1. How long we will hold your Personal Data for will vary and will be determined by the following criteria:
      * the purpose for which we are using it – Check Point will need to keep the data for as long as is necessary for that purpose; and
      * legal obligations – laws or regulation may set a minimum period for which we have to keep your Personal Data.
  9.  **YOUR RIGHTS**
    1. In all the above cases in which we collect, use or store your Personal Data, you may have the following rights and, in most cases, you can exercise them free of charge. These rights include:
      * the right to obtain information regarding the processing of your Personal Data and access to the Personal Data which we hold about you;
      * the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your Personal Data at any time. Please note, however, that we may still be entitled to process your Personal Data if we have another legitimate reason for doing so. For example, we may need to retain Personal Data to comply with a legal obligation;
      * in some circumstances, the right to receive some Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and/or request that we transmit those data to a third party where this is technically feasible. Please note that this right only applies to Personal Data which you have provided directly to Check Point;
      * the right to request that we rectify your Personal Data if it is inaccurate or incomplete;
      * the right to request that we erase your Personal Data in certain circumstances. Please note that there may be circumstances where you ask us to erase your Personal Data but we are legally entitled to retain it;
      * the right to request that we restrict our processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances. Again, there may be circumstances where you ask us to restrict our processing of your Personal Data but we are legally entitled to refuse that request; and
      * the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection regulator if you think that any of your rights have been infringed by us.
    2. You can exercise your rights by contacting us using the details listed in paragraph 11 below.
  10.  **DESIGNATED REPRESENTATIVE**
    1. Check Point’s registered office may be contacted using the following contact information:  
 _Address:_|  Check Point Software Technologies Ltd.,  
5 Shlomo Kaplan Street,  
Tel Aviv 67897,  
Israel  
Attention: Legal Department  
---|---  
 _Email Address:_| [privacy_inquiries@checkpoint.com](mailto:privacy_inquiries\(at\)checkpoint.com)  
    2. Check Point’s designated representative in the EU may be contacted using the following contact information:  

  11.  **QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS**
    1. If you have any questions or concerns about Check Point’s handling of your Personal Data, or about this Policy, please contact our Privacy Officer using the following contact information:  
 _Address:_|  Check Point Software Technologies Ltd.,  
5 Shlomo Kaplan Street,  
Tel Aviv 67897,  
Israel  
Attention: Legal Department  
---|---  
 _Email Address:_| [privacy_inquiries@checkpoint.com](mailto:privacy_inquiries\(at\)checkpoint.com)  
  
We are usually able to resolve privacy questions or concerns promptly and effectively. If you are not satisfied with the response you receive from our Privacy Officer, you may escalate concerns to the applicable privacy regulator in your jurisdiction. Upon request, Check Point’s Privacy Officer will provide you with the contact information for that regulator.

### CHECK POINT COOKIES NOTICE

This Cookies Notice provides you with information about the cookies we use and why we use them. It should be read together with the **Check Point Website** **Terms and Conditions** (governing your use of the Webpages and Services) and the **Check Point Privacy Policy** (outlining our practices regarding your personal data).

This Cookies Notice applies to cookies used on any Check Point website with the Check Point domain and the Check Point operated websites listed below including (each a **“Webpage”** and together the **“Webpages”** ):

  * • [www.cybertalk.org](https://www.cybertalk.org/)
  * • [www.cpcheckme.com](https://www.cpcheckme.com/)
  * • [www.zonealarm.com](http://www.zonealarm.com/)

This Cookies Notice also applies to cookies used on any Check Point service including these listed below, which may not be an exhaustive list (each a “ **Service** ” and together the “ **Services** ”):

  * • Check Point Support;
  * • Check Point Mobile Security Solutions;
  * • ThreatCloud;
  * • Capsule Cloud;
  * • Capsule Docs Cloud Service; and
  * • SandBlast Cloud Service

References to **“We”** and **“Us”** in this Cookies Notice means Check Point Software Technologies Ltd., 5 Shlomo Kaplan Street, Tel Aviv 67897, Israel, and other affiliates or companies within the Check Point international group.

Unless otherwise stated, the definitions used in the **Check Point Website** **Terms and Conditions** are adopted in this Cookies Notice.

 **A. WHAT ARE COOKIES?**

Cookies are small text files that are sent to and temporarily stored on your computer, smartphone or other device for accessing the internet whenever you visit a website.

 **B. WHY DO WE USE COOKIES?**

We use Cookies for a variety of reasons, including:

  * • To improve the functionality and performance of the Webpages and Services (including your user experience) and to make sure the Webpages and Services perform as you expect them to
  * • To prevent any potential disruptions or cyber attacks to the Webpages or Services
  * • To distinguish you from other users of the Webpages and Services, and
  * • To allow us to tailor Webpage and Service content to better suit your interests and needs
  *  

 **C. TYPES OF COOKIES WE USE**

We use the following types of cookies on our Webpages:

 **Cookies**|  **Description**|  **Duration**  
---|---|---  
 **Analytics and Integrity cookies**|  These help us analyze how you use the Webpages and Services and allow us to identify what you like, do not like and how we can improve things for you. They also allow for site integrity, such as remembering when you are logged into a secure area.| These cookies will remain until they are deleted.  
 **Session cookies**|  These cookies are essential to ensure performance of our Webpages and allow you to use our online services. You will be unable to load our pages if you block these cookies. We also use session cookies to save your language preferences or display search queries.| These cookies will expire when you leave the Webpages.  
 **Functionality cookies**|  These cookies are not essential but they enhance your use of the Webpages. Pre-filling of fields is one example of what these cookies do, as are social media cookies which allow for the sharing of content.| These cookies typically expire after 2 years.  
 **Authentication cookies**|  These provide you with access to User Center: our secured login area and main portal (“User Center”). Without this cookie, you will be unable to register or log in, and thus be unable to access User Center.| These cookies typically expire after 6 years  
 **‘Strictly necessary’ cookies**|  These cookies are essential to ensure performance of the Webpages and include Session Cookies.| These cookies typically expire after 3 months  
 **Targeting or advertising cookies**| 

These cookies allow us to display promotions and advertisements from external websites that may be of interest to you. We have also signed a written data processing agreement with Google based on a template created by Google in association with data protection authorities. For further information on this, please contact Google Ireland Ltd., Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland or visit [www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html) and/or [www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy](http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy).

For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web-browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) if you are in the United States, or [youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/) if you are outside the United States.

| These cookies typically expire after 3 months  
  
Most of the cookies we use do not save any information that can identify you as an individual. Instead, we receive general and anonymized information from these cookies regarding all users of our Webpages and Services, including, but not limited to: the services accessed, the browser and operating systems used, activity data relating to the use of documents, time and date stamps, the type of user device and the cities that users are located in. We only collect part of your IP address in a form that does not permit recognition of or mapping to a specific individual.

Where you have provided us with information about you as an individual (for example, by registering with us), we may use information collected using cookies to identify you as an individual and to inform you about products or services that may be of interest to you.

We use this collected data for the purposes of troubleshooting, internet based advertising, informing you about products or services that may be of interest to you and improving the services offered.

 **D. MANAGING YOUR COOKIES**

By using the Webpages and/or closing the pop-up cookie notice, you consent to the use of cookies on the Webpages. If you do not consent to the use of cookies on the Webpages, you should immediately leave the Webpages and/or change your browser settings to block cookies.

The browsers of most computers, smartphones and other web-enabled devices are typically set up to accept cookies. If you wish to amend your cookie preferences for the Webpages, you can do this at any time by changing your browser settings. Your browser’s ‘help’ function will tell you how to do this. You do not have to accept cookies, however, please note that cookies are often used to enable and improve certain functions on the Webpages. If you choose to block cookies through your browser settings, it is likely to affect how the Webpages work and you may not be able to access all or parts of the Webpages.

For more information about how to disable cookies, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web-browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) if you are in the United States, or [youronlinechoices.eu](http://youronlinechoices.eu/) if you are outside the United States.

 **E. CONTACT US**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Cookies Notice can be sent to us using the contact details set out below:

checkpoint.com/about-us/contact-us  
Or: [privacy_inquiries@checkpoint.com](mailto:privacy_inquiries\(at\)checkpoint.com)

 **United States**  
Check Point Software Technologies Inc.  
959 Skyway Road, Suite 300  
San Carlos, CA 94070

 **International**  
Check Point Software Technologies Ltd.  
5 Shlomo Kaplan Street  
Tel Aviv 67897, Isr

### CHECK POINT WEBSITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS

 **PLEASE READ THESE TERMS CAREFULLY BEFORE YOU USE THIS SITE.**

 **A. DEFINITIONS**

 **“Check Point”** means Check Point Software Technologies Ltd and any affiliated entities within the Check Point Group.

 **“Materials”** means any information and/or software available via the Site.

 **“Intellectual Property”** means (i) patents, patent disclosures and inventions (whether patentable or not); (ii) trademarks, service marks, trade dress, trade names, logos, corporate names and domain names, together with all of the goodwill associated therewith; (iii) copyrights and copyrightable works (including computer programs), mask works, and rights in data and databases; (iv) trade secrets, know-how and other confidential information; and (v) all other intellectual property rights, in each case whether registered or unregistered and including all applications and rights to apply for and be granted, renewals or extensions of, such rights, and all similar or equivalent rights or forms of protection in any part of the world.

 **“Products”** shall include all software tools created and/or utilized by Check Point to deliver the Services, and shall include any online or offline applications, application plug-ins running on any platform or device, and application programming interfaces, used for this purpose.

 **“Services”** means all professional data security and IT security services which may be performed by Check Point including, but not limited to product support, vulnerability scanning, security consultation, system hardening, incident response, penetration testing, and consulting services.

 **“Site”** means all content, including the Materials, included on this website ([checkpoint.com](https://www.checkpoint.com/)).

In these Terms, the words “you” and “your” refer to all visitors and users of this Site, and the words **“we”** , **“us”** , **“our”** , and **“Check Point”** refer to Check Point (as defined above), a company registered in the State of Israel at  Check Point Software Technologies Ltd., 5 Shlomo Kaplan Street, Tel Aviv 67897, Israel.

 **B. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS**

By accessing and using this Site, you accept and agree to be bound by these Terms. If you are using this Site on behalf of a company or other corporate entity or institution, you represent that you have the legal authority to bind such entity to these Terms, in which case the terms **“you”** or **“your”** shall refer to such entity.

If you do not agree to these terms, now or at any time, please do not use this site, our products and/or our services.

 **C. LIMITED LICENSE**

The Materials on this Site are provided by Check Point as a service to its customers and those persons visiting the Site and may be used for informational and non-commercial purposes only.

All the content on this Site is protected by Intellectual Property belonging to Check Point. Check Point reserves all of its rights in and pertaining to such copyright. No portion of this Site may be reproduced in any form, or by any means, without prior written permission from Check Point.

Check Point hereby grants you a limited, non-exclusive, non-sublicensable, non-transferable, revocable right to access and use the Site and related Intellectual Property copyrights to:

  *  **(1)** View, download or print one copy of the information found on the Site solely for your personal, non-commercial use in support of the use or marketing of Check Point and its Products; or
  *  **(2)** If you have a pre-existing business relationship with Check Point, you may download Materials for use in the furtherance of, and subject to the terms and conditions of, the provisions of your separate written agreement with Check Point. Please see the General User License Agreement detailed on our website for further details.

Additionally, some Materials may be made available only subject to certain additional license terms which may accompany or are provided with such Materials, and your download and use of those Materials will be subject to those additional terms and conditions.

This is a license, not a transfer of title in any Intellectual Property, the contents of this Site and/or the Materials. The license is also subject to the following restrictions: you may not: (a) modify the Materials or other contents of this Site or use them for any commercial purpose; (b) decompile, reverse engineer, or disassemble Materials except and only to the extent required to be permitted by applicable law; (c) remove any copyright or other proprietary notices from the Materials; (d) use the Materials or other contents of this Site in a manner inconsistent with the scope of the license granted in these terms.

The trademarks, logos and service marks ( **“Marks”** ) displayed on this Site are the property of Check Point or its licensors. You are not permitted to use these Marks without the prior written consent of Check Point.

 **D. USER SUBMISSIONS**

Any comments, information or other materials posted to this Site or transmitted to Check Point such as questions, comments, suggestions, or the like regarding Check Point Products, this Site and the Materials ( **“Feedback”** ) will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary unless expressly agreed otherwise in writing by Check Point prior to your submission.

Check Point shall have no obligations to you with regard to its use or disclosure of such Feedback, and Check Point shall have a worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully-paid right to use, reproduce, prepare derivative works of, perform, display and distribute the Feedback, including any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such Feedback, for any and all purposes without limitation, and to authorize others to do so as well. You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from this Site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, or other material that would violate any law.  Check Point may, in its sole discretion, remove or delete any Feedback, for any reason, without prior notice.

 **E. ELIGIBILITY TO USE THE SITE**

By using the Site, you represent that (i) your use of the Site is solely for your internal, personal and non-commercial purposes, and in order to learn about Check Point Products and Services, and (ii) your use of the Site does not (and will not) violate any applicable law or regulation and is (and will be) in strict compliance with these Terms. If Check Point is informed or has reason to believe that you are not eligible or that you become ineligible to use the Site, your use may be terminated or suspended without notice, at Check Point’s sole discretion.

By accessing and using the Site, you agree that you will not, and will not permit any third party, in any way, to:

  * • Use the Site and/or any Materials in violation of these Terms and/or any applicable law or regulation;
  * • Use the Site in connection with any commercial activity;
  * • Use or launch any automated system, including without limitation, any “robots”, “spiders”, or “offline readers”, that accesses the Site in a manner that sends more request messages to the Check Point servers in a given period of time than a human can reasonably produce in the same period by using a conventional on-line web browser;
  * • Use or launch any data mining or any similar data gathering and extraction tools, in connection with the Site (including by using software, scripts or automated agents and bots);
  * • Use the Site in any manner that damages, disables, overburdens, or impairs the Site, or Check Point systems or servers, and/or otherwise interferes with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the Site;
  * • Mirror or frame the Site or any part of it on any other website or web page.
  * • Attempt to gain unauthorized access to any part of the Site and/or Materials;

Check Point reserves the right to terminate or suspend your use of the Site and/or Materials, without prior notice, if it has reason to believe that you are not using the Site and/or Materials in accordance with these Terms.

 **F. GENERAL DISCLAIMER**

Although Check Point has attempted to provide accurate information on the Site and in the Materials, Check Point assumes no responsibility for the accuracy of any such information.

All information and Materials provided on this Site are provided “as is” without warranty of any kind, express, implied, statutory or otherwise, including without limitation any warranty of suitability, non-infringement or fitness for any particular purpose. Check Point shall have no liability for any damages whatsoever (including without limitation any lost profits, lost data, loss of use, or costs of procurement of substituted goods or services, whether direct, indirect , special or consequential in nature) arising out of or in connection with the Site and/or Materials.

 **G. THIRD PARTY LINKS**

This Site may contain links to third party sites. The linked sites are not under the control of Check Point, and Check Point is not responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any information, opinions, advice or statements made on these linked sites. Access to any of these linked sites is at the user’s own risk.

 **H. APPLICABLE LAW**

This site is controlled by Check Point from its offices within the United States. Check Point makes no representation that Products and/or Services offered by the Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to them from territories where their content is illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this Site from other locations do so under their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. Not all Products or Services mentioned may be available in your country. Please contact your local sales representative for information as to Products and Services available in your country.

 **I. TERMINATION**

Check Point shall have the right to terminate the license granted to you to use, interact with, download and use the Site, Materials made available from this Site at any time if you are found to be in breach any of these terms and conditions, or for any other reason. Upon a termination, you agree to immediately destroy any Materials in your possession or control.

 **I. GOVERNING LAW**

Check Point reserves the right to change these terms and conditions at any time without notice by altering or updating this posting. Some of the Services or Materials available on this Site (e.g. software downloadable from this Site) may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages at this Site. These Terms, including any claim arising out of these terms, shall be governed by the laws of the State of Israel and any proceedings arising out or in connection with this Site shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of _Tel-Aviv, Israel._

 **J. MODIFICATIONS OF THE TERMS**

We may modify these Terms at any time at our sole discretion, and such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified Terms. Your continued use of the Site shall be deemed as acceptance of the modified Terms.
